-DOCSTART-

NASA	B-ORG
launched	O
a	O
new	O
satellite	O
from	O
Cape	B-LOC
Canaveral	I-LOC
on	O
Monday	O
.	O

The	O
satellite	O
,	O
named	O
Landsat	B-MISC
9	I-MISC
,	O
will	O
monitor	O
earth	O
resources	O
.	O

Mission	O
control	O
is	O
located	O
at	O
Johnson	B-MISC
Space	I-MISC
Center	I-MISC
in	O
Houston	B-LOC
.	O

-DOCSTART-

Lionel	B-PER
Messi	I-PER
scored	O
twice	O
for	O
Inter	B-ORG
Miami	I-ORG
against	O
Orlando	B-ORG
City	I-ORG
.	O

The	O
match	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
MLS	B-MISC
regular	O
season	O
.	O

Miami	B-ORG
fans	O
celebrated	O
at	O
DRV	B-MISC
PNK	I-MISC
Stadium	I-MISC
.	O

-DOCSTART-

Angela	B-PER
Merkel	I-PER
met	O
with	O
Emmanuel	B-PER
Macron	I-PER
in	O
Paris	B-LOC
to	O
discuss	O
climate	O
policy	O
.	O

They	O
agreed	O
to	O
revisit	O
the	O
Paris	B-MISC
Agreement	I-MISC
targets	O
.	O

Germany	B-LOC
and	O
France	B-LOC
have	O
taken	O
leadership	O
roles	O
in	O
EU	B-ORG
climate	O
efforts	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-

The	O
iPhone	B-MISC
15	I-MISC
was	O
announced	O
by	O
Apple	B-ORG
at	O
its	O
annual	O
event	O
in	O
Cupertino	B-LOC
.	O

Tim	B-PER
Cook	I-PER
introduced	O
new	O
features	O
like	O
USB-C	B-MISC
charging	O
and	O
improved	O
battery	O
life	O
.	O

Apple	B-ORG
fans	O
shared	O
their	O
reactions	O
online	O
.	O

-DOCSTART-

Serena	B-PER
Williams	I-PER
returned	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
at	O
Wimbledon	B-MISC
after	O
a	O
year-long	O
break	O
.	O

She	O
faced	O
Emma	B-PER
Raducanu	I-PER
in	O
the	O
second	O
round	O
.	O

The	O
All	B-ORG
England	I-ORG
Club	I-ORG
was	O
packed	O
with	O
fans	O
.	O

BBC	B-ORG
broadcasted	O
the	O
match	O
live	O
.	O

